Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
The Diamond Kingdom launched an attack on the Clover border village of Khitan to pave the way for a full-blown invasion.
But the Golden Dawn, led by Captain Vongins, was quick to reinforce the village's defenses, and the tide of battle seemed to be turning in favor of the Clover Kingdom.
Wind magic. Swift white bow!
I thought I saw a familiar speck down here. So what brings you to Khitan, Asta?
If you got those injuries while fighting someone like I think you did, then that must mean you got stronger again.
I won't lose. Got that?
Not just me! Looks like you've gotten more powerful too!
But I won't lose either. No way!
I won't lose.
Go away!
Magoo Playstation
So how dare you ask?
I won't lose.
Please tell me the confidence in the showroom's scenario.
Thank you.
He's actually smiling!
Am I going crazy or have you gotten taller since the last time I saw you?
You know barely says a word to me, but this guy gets a whole conversation?
Oh yeah. By a couple of inches, I think.
It should be my turn for a growth spurt! No fair!
Well, you won't beat me! I'll at eight by tomorrow, and then I'll be the one looking down on you!
No! Not happening.
You think you're so great just because you're tall?
What do you think you're doing, Yuno?
Who is this guy and why are you talking to him so much?
He's the thing! Quit ignoring me!
What's with the squeaky crying bug pulling on your face?
Wait! Is that Sylph?
I've never seen Yuno make that face before! She must be really powerful!
You tell me who this banged-up spiky-haired pimp squeak is right now!
I'm a pimp squeak?
He and I lived together when we were younger.
Wait! You what? Seriously? You loved what this banged?
That's right. We ate together and studied together, too. Not to mention sleeping and taking baths together.
Sleeping together? And bathing?
I know it's been a while, but I wanted to thank you for boldly risking your life to save my lunch the last time we saw each other.
You're like a prince of a fairy tale.
Yeah, that's right. I remember you now.
Here! A hearty after-battle snack just for you!
Thanks.
Oh, and a little something extra to make it even yummier.
Okay.
What's her story? She's obviously got it bad for Yuno.
My name's Charmy, by the way. Would it be alright if I called you Yuno?
Yeah, that's fine.
Great!
Nice taster.
I'm glad.
My Sylph's intuition tells me this little girl's no threat.
Sorry about last time. I didn't mean to wind up on top of you.
Oh, don't worry your pretty head about that. I know I didn't lose any sleep over it.
On top of her! No!
What?
Hey! Are you trying to cast some kind of spell on Yuno to make him like you?
Don't you dare, you little brat!
Huh? What kind of creature is that? I wonder if it tastes good.
She's a wind spirit, Charmy, and we don't eat spirits, okay?
You two need to back up before I get really mad!
Yuno is mine and nobody else is!
You'd better be careful who you're calling a little brat.
I'll have you know I'm 19.
A worldly woman who can teach sweet Yuno a thing or two.
And my sexiness doesn't need any magical enhancements either.
Sexiness? You've got to be kidding me, you fun-sized five head!
Oh yeah?
Maybe you should take a look in the mirror sometime, Shrippy!
How dare you!
I'll show you what happens when you toss back to us still!
Yeah! Let's see it!
That's it!
I'll try you up and hit you for dinner!
You're gone now!
Charmy, please just let it go!
Well, I think that's enough.
Looks like you guys are having fun.
Can I join the party?
Hey, where have you been?
Who's he?
That's Finral. He's one of the senior Black Bulls.
You might have heard of him before.
Not at all.
Not surprising.
He's one of the elite Golden Dawn after-
Oh my!
What have we here?
If it isn't my big brother.
It's been simply ages.
And of all places to run into you again.
Of course you'd be here.
Who's that?
Your pitiful fighting skills are a disgrace to our whole family.
What business do you have in battle?
Hey, Finral, who's this jerk and why's he saying all that rude stuff to you?
My little brother.
This is Longris Vod, Vice Captain of the Golden Dawn.
Seriously?
And I assume you're still performing your duties as the Black Bulls' pack mule.
If you weren't so hopelessly incompetent, it would be you carrying on the Vod family legacy instead of me.
You're wrong!
Finral's an awesome fighter!
Like in our last battle!
We wouldn't have been able to take the enemy down if it weren't for him!
You mean he actually managed to make himself useful for once?
Now there's a shock.
Hey, that's your big brother you're talking about!
Don't you think you ought to show some respect?
Why would I show him respect?
It's not like he's earned it.
Listen, jerk!
It's okay, Asta, really.
I mean, it's all true, right?
No, it's not.
Just drop it.
The Diamond Kingdom's troops have been more or less wiped out.
They're finished.
Thanks to our captain and his world tree magic.
So your sad little squad can run along home now.
But tell me, when did the Black Bulls start running a daycare service?
Have you been downgraded from packed mule to babysitter?
Looking after these snot-nosed brats, you must be simply mortified.
Who are you calling a snot-nosed brat?
Only a girl who wants to have this kind of shark!
That's enough.
You can mock me all you want to, Longris.
I don't care.
But them?
Don't you dare mock my squadmates!
Not ever!
Wow.
So there's some fight in you after all.
I'm done playing.
I swear on the honor of the eight shining generous.
I will have your hands!
From here I thought we'd dealt with all of you people.
If I attack, my spatial magic will wind up hitting the villagers that are trapped in there too.
That's right!
So what are you going to do now?
Help us!
Please!
No!
We're all going to die!
No time to hesitate.
Well, too bad.
I suppose they'll have to make the ultimate sacrifice for their country.
Stop!
Huh?
How could you just kill your own people like that?
It's our duty to protect them!
There are only going to be more casualties if I do nothing.
No way!
I'm not giving up on anybody!
Finral Charmy, let's go!
Right!
Roger!
Watch this, you know.
All right.
Show me what you've got.
What could he hope to do in that state?
Retreat as quickly as possible.
Cotton creation magic!
Fluffy sheep cushion!
Who the hell do you think you are?
Don't challenge me!
What?
Spatial magic?
My new chrismatics been completely nullified.
How is that even possible?
What?
What have you done, you brat?
Thanks for that, Yuno, I owe you!
No problem. Nice fighting as always, Asta.
He's smiling again!
Longris!
It's true that I could never hope to best you, but someday the Black Bulls will best the Golden Dawn!
Yeah!
So, World Tree Magic, is that the only kind you got? Nothing else?
What are you implying?
Well, I'm the kind of guy who goes with his gut instinct.
Vangence, if you don't mind, lose the mask.
My face isn't exactly fit for others to see.
What, you wear that thing because you're super ugly or something?
Hey, it's okay. I promise not to laugh, alright?
I understand, Yami. You are suspicious of me, aren't you?
You think I might be the leader of the Eye of the Midnight Sun?
Frankly, I do, yeah.
His light magic, Vangence's World Tree Magic.
They're different, sure, but something isn't right.
They've got the same build, similar voices.
Most of all, their key feels the same.
Still.
It's been ten years since we met, hasn't it?
That's correct.
So we've had a pretty long history, you and me.
Meeting on the battlefield, fighting alongside each other from time to time,
even eventually becoming captains together.
Remember how bouncy Nozel's braid used to be?
I'm not saying we're especially friendly, but we do go back a while.
There's something about him that I feel in you, too.
So come on.
Show me your face.
Very well.
Those are some pretty nasty scars.
Had them long?
Always.
My whole life.
They called me a cursed child.
Is that right?
Not even magic can heal these marks.
People found them eerie to look at, and they feared me.
I was a nobleman's illegitimate child.
Until I was eight years old, I lived in the Forsaken Realm.
But then the nobleman's heir passed away.
He summoned me, brought me into his house to be his successor.
Fortunately, I possessed great power, and my magic was a curiosity.
But even there, my face was despised, and the nobleman's wife, my foster mother, treated me cruelly.
I wouldn't wish the sort of childhood I had on anyone.
But I don't want to see and truette her at a time.
It seems like you've been through a lot.
Yes, but that's also when I met Julius.
He paid no mind to my appearance, instead seeing only my strength.
Incredible! What was that magic you were just using?
Um, World Tree magic.
Now there's a marvelous name, and well-suited for such marvelous magic.
I've never seen anything like it.
Um...
Truly, it's such a lovely spell.
Like you want to safeguard everything.
Wrap it in kindness.
Now then, you absolutely must become a magic knight!
I...
No?
It's not that I don't want to, but the magic knights?
I never thought I could join them.
I mean, with this face.
Now, now, that isn't anything to worry about.
What?
I'm serious.
Your face isn't something you ought to be ashamed of.
However, if it bothers you that much...
Well, in that case...
I'll give you this mask!
But, Julia, sir, this is so...
Tacky.
But I worked on it so hard!
I was happy.
And I vowed to devote my Grimoire to his service.
Well, that's a familiar story.
His face and bearing both resemble the Light Mages.
But I'm not picking up any trace of power in those scars.
No tricks at work here.
He's not showing me an illusion.
And more than that, his key tells me he's not lying.
So, I guess the resemblance is purely coincidence.
Right, well, sorry.
No.
I'm glad I got the chance to show you who I am.
Thank you, Yami.
Sure thing.
Captain Vongens, do you read me?
The Diamond Kingdom has begun to retreat.
Very good.
Don't pursue those who flee.
Concentrate all your efforts on healing the injured.
Understood.
We should get to work.
With the number of prisoners we've captured,
transporting them all will be difficult.
Yeah.
Oh, hey, I got a guy who comes in real handy for that kind of thing.
And we can work him hard.
Not too hard, no.
Some sweet lady must be talking about me.
I guess things have gotten pretty quiet.
We should probably go look for the captain.
Sounds good.
Already?
See you later, you know!
Yeah.
Bye, Asta.
Don't eat stuff you find on the ground.
Hey, that's not fair!
It's been years since I've done that.
I was wondering if there was a way I could get in touch with you sometime.
Hey!
Stay away from my yodo, you steamy raccoon!
Blow my eyes!
Are you trying to blind me with your sparkles, you evil head fast?
Okay, that's it!
I'm going to fry you up for sure!
How do you see me?
Next time I'm going to have fry both of them!
Let's go.
I can't believe I actually said that!
The worst squad picking a fight with the best one!
Have I gone totally crazy?
What's the matter?
You got a headache or something?
Oh, man!
I can't wait to swing a sword again!
I can get a duck that you don't nearly long enough!
Stress-eating, Charmy!
How can they eat right now?
Didn't they hear what I said?
Whoa!
There's nothing like a heaping helping of dessert for turning a frown upside down!
Hey, not bad.
Honestly, what a vulgar bunch they are.
You should really choose your friends more carefully, you know.
Aren't you embarrassed to be seen with people like that?
Why would I be?
I've never felt that way once.
I'm very proud of Asta.
He's my rival.
A simpleton like that's your rival!
And for what, anyway?
Are you two in some kind of competition?
That's right, yes.
That was a little abrupt back there.
Should you have said a better goodbye?
I thought you and that handsome Golden Dawn fellow were old friends.
It's fine!
I'll see him on another battlefield someday.
After all, me and him, we're aiming to become the Wizard King!
The Wizard King?
Ha!
That's ridiculous!
And you aren't even embarrassed to say it, are you?
But maybe commoners just don't feel shame,
especially one who's been raised high above his station.
The Great Yuno, a backwoods commoner chosen by the four-leaf grimoire.
I don't know what your problem is, sir Smirky,
but I don't let anybody mock my Yuno!
There's no rule saying that a commoner can't be the Wizard King.
Huh?
First, of course, I'll become captain of the Golden Dawn.
Will you?
Have you forgotten the fact that I'm our squad's current vice-captain?
Yuno!
Good.
The area's clear and we've treated the majority of the ingi-
What did I miss?
The Diamond troops have withdrawn,
though a number remain in our custody.
Kitan is safe, sir.
Thank you, Marks.
Let's begin repairing damaged buildings
and setting up temporary shelters at once.
Yes, sir.
Now then, what is this really about?
Their attempted invasion didn't strike me as a very serious one.
What are they truly after?
Fascinating.
A sylph.
Offensive spatial spells.
Parasitic world tree magic.
It sounds as if they had much to contend with.
Those crumbling old generals may have been powerful once,
but their day has passed.
Now the time has come for we mage knights
to step up and usher in a new age of generals.
We'll be right back.
Get set!
Shiaを伸ばしたら届くすだけど
行ったり来たり消えたりバッタリな
その場その場しのゲームみたいなシーンが
たくさん
これファブリスイートで拡散
どうぞたくさん
ここでまた
全て合算したら発散すれば
愛だろう恋だろう
名もは僕らが通り越して
まだ名前などないその輝きも
己の中に見つけるんでしょ
天上天下
皆唯一がドックスソング
ここはここにいるってことで
あれでもないこれでもない今この瞬間
ライトライト
どこでいても変わらないでも
yeah yeah yeah
不当たり前なの
何もなんでもないもの
できちゃって
ここだって
ここは僕でいたいな
ご視聴ありがとうございました
Slow down Asta
Unbelievable
And you ate together
You're ridiculous
You even took those together
What's her problem?
No idea
Well that's a load off
Don't know what I would have done
if Vonjin's hat actually turned out
to be that licked guy
Black Clover page 54
Never again
Hey maybe I ought to give him
another goofy mask as an apology
Alright
Actually
Bye
B